Alumni Association; Records ua801
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Theatre Alumni Association, 1932-1974; Undated; 7; 1.03 cubic ft.
  - By-Laws and Letter, 1963 June 15-1963 June 18 (Box 1 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 15)
  - Futterer Recordings-Brochures, 1963-1965; Undated (Box 1 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 16)
  - Futterer Recordings Sales Report, 1963-1971 (Box 2 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 1)
  - Futterer Recordings, Notes and Invoices, 1963; 1967; Undated (Box 2 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 2)
  - Futterer Lectureships, 1964-1973 (Box 2 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 3)
  - Futterer Recordings, Clippings, 1964-1966; 1968; 1970; Undated (Box 2 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 4)
  - Donahue Books Donated to University Libraries, 1966-1967; Undated (Box 2 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 5)
  - Futterer Portrait, 1966-1970 (Box 2 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, General, 1969-1974; Undated (Box 2 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 7)
  - Futterer Memorial Lounge Dedication, 1974 May 08 (Box 2 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 8)
  - "Through the Years"-Playbill, Undated (Box 2 (7-Theatre Alumni Association), Folder 7)
- Deceased Alumni Files, 1969-2010; Undated; 8; 41 cubic ft.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  This collection includes thousands of files previously maintained by the Alumni Association about individual graduates from the 20th Century. The contents of the files vary and range from simply housing an obituary to holding newsclippings, correspondence and other materials detailing a graduate's professional life. This often includes a ca. 1969 all alumni survey, class notes submissions and questionnaires targeted to specific graduating classes or campus organizations. At present time there is no master list of files, but they may be accessed by archives staff. Please contact the department with any questions.
  For information about 19th Century graudates of the New York State Normal School and the New York State Normal College, please refer to the 1894 Historical Sketch of the State Normal College at Albany, NY held by University Archives, which contains handwritten annotations and updates through 1918.
- Web Archives, 2014 July 10-2016 September 22; 9; 459 captures
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Web crawling is managed through the Internet Archive's Archive-It service. This page includes links to both the university's collection and the Internet Archive's public collection.
  Surface-level crawling of www.albany.edu is performed daily which should includes most top-level webpages. Separate targeted crawls of every albany.edu subdomain are performed monthly to attempt to gather all content. This includes: www.albany.edu, www.rna.albany.edu, www.ctg.albany.edu, www.ualbanysports.com, www.albany.edu/rockefeller, www.albany.edu/cela, www.albany.edu/asrc, m.albany.edu, library.albany.edu, events.albany.edu, cstar.cestm.albany.edu, csda.albany.edu, and alumni.albany.edu
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Web Archives
  - http://www.alumni.albany.edu - University Archives collection, 2014 July 10-2016 September 17 (Web-archive 1)
  - WARC file for http://www.alumni.albany.edu, (please see https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Web_ARChive for more details), 2014 July 10-2016 September 17 (Warc 1)
    WARC files are very large and difficult to work with. Your request may take time to process, and we may be unable to deliver your request remotely. Please consult an archivist if you are interested in researching with web archives.
  - http://www.alumni.albany.edu - Internet Archive collection, 2014 July 10-2016 September 22 (Web-archive 2)